&gt；&gt；steve kinney：有，我们很快就会看一看。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: There is,
we're going to take a look real quick.
我会关掉这张幻灯片。
I'll switch off this slide.
我们将看一下“油漆风暴”示例。
We'll look at the "Paint
Storming" example.
我们会先看一眼，我们现在就会看到它会引起油漆风暴。
We'll take a first look and we'll see
right now it causes a paint storm.
我们想要做的是折射它，所以
What we want to do is we
want to refractor it, so
当鼠标进入时，它会向上移动到它自己的层。
that when the mouse enters it
moves up to it's own layer.
然后当它结束时，我们把它放回去，或者当鼠标离开的时候。
And then when it ends, we put it
back down or when the mouse leaves.
所以让我们来看一下代码
So let's take a look at the code and
那我会给你一些时间来玩这个。
then I'll give you some time
to play around with this.
因此，让我们首先在浏览器中实际查看它。
So let's actually look at
it in the browser first.
我不再需要特殊的，超级特殊的模式了。
I don't need the special,
super special mode anymore.
我们要画风暴，我有这个红色的盒子，点击它，看看
We're going to paint storming, I've got
this red box, click on it, look at that
小小的绿色阵列油漆跟随它，让我们刷新这个，看起来很有趣。
little green array paint follow it,
let's refresh this, it's fun to watch.
我们要画，就像一场小小的油漆风暴，
We're going to paint, and
it's like a little paint storm,
它只是重绘每一个像素。
it's just repainting every pixel.
好吧这是什么？
All right, what is this?
因此，如果我们查看代码并查看
So if we look at the code and
we look under
搬家的箱子，以为那是另一个，油漆风暴。
moving boxes, thought that was
the other one, paint storming.
酷毙了。我们在油漆风暴下寻找。
Cool.
We look under paint storming.
忽略有一个解决方案目录，它并不重要。
Ignore that there is a solutions
directory, it is not important.
不关注解决方案目录。
Pay no attention to
the solutions directory.
我们将使用jQuery制作动画，因为10年前，
We are going to use jQuery for
animation because 10 years ago, and
这就是我们现在正在做的。
that's what we're doing right now.
你可以看到这是使用JavaScript来调整
And you can see that that's
using JavaScript to adjust
左边，好吗？
the marginLeft, all right?
改变内联风格也就不足为奇了，
And it's not surprising that
that changes the inline style,
这会触发重新粉刷，在这种情况下，对吗？
which triggers a repaint,
in this case, right?
我们在每一帧上都这样做，让我们实际测量一下。
And we're doing it on every frame, and
let's actually measure it for a second.
让我们看看这里发生了什么。
Let's see what's going on here.
我们会刷新。
We'll refresh.
我要关掉闪烁的油漆
I'm going to turn off the paint flashing
当您还尝试收集性能指标时。
when you also try to collect
the performance metrics.
否则，事情将变得糟糕得可怕，因为浏览器也试图
Otherwise, things will be horrifyingly
bad because the browser is also trying to
画那些绿色的方块，你会得到噪音。
paint all those green squares and
you'll get noise.
所以你关掉油漆闪光。
So you turn off the paint flashing.
单击它。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
Click it.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
这是把那个盒子超过500像素的过程，对吗？
this is the process of getting
that box 500 pixels over, right?
我们可以放大，我们可以看到一些JavaScript，
And we can zoom in,
we can see that there's some JavaScript,
有一个重新计算的风格，有一个布局，有一个更新层托盘。
there is a recalculated style, there's
a layout, there's an update layer tray.
合成一些层，我们反复这样做。
Composite some layers, and
we're doing this repeatedly.
所以不这样做会很棒，因为这是工作。
So it would be great to not do this,
cuz this is work.
不做工作比做工作快。
Not doing work is faster than doing work.
所以我们看一下代码。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：那里
So we look at the code.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: There
是这个移动类，它似乎知道如何让它一路走过来，而且
is this move class, which seems to know
how to get it all the way over, and
看起来确实有转变。
there does seem to be a transition.
因此，如果我们应用Move类而不是作为jQuery进行操作，
So if we apply that move class
instead of doing it as a jQuery,
我们可以只使用CSS转换，对吗？
we could just use CSS transitions, right?
似乎在单击上我们想说的是添加Move类和
Seems like maybe on click what we want
to say is add that move class and
它应该会移动。
it should move.
但我们仍然在制作自己的图层，同时移动，所以
But then we're still making it's own
layer and moving at the same time so
我们可能需要编写一些额外的JavaScript才能移动它。
we're probably going to need to write some
extra JavaScript to be able to move it.
所以现在轮到你试一试，然后我们一起做。
So this is your turn to give it a shot,
then we'll do it together.
所以我要把这张幻灯片放在
So I'm gonna put this slide up for
一秒钟，然后我会回到我们之前看到的另一个代码，然后
a second, but then I'm gonna go back to
that other code that we saw earlier, and
那就是我要把它冻结一段时间的地方。
that'll be where I freeze it for
a little bit.
但你的工作是摆脱jQuery动画，
But your job is to get rid
of that jQuery animation,
使用CSS过渡，但是当鼠标进入时，当我们想要添加将改变，
use the CSS transition, but when the mouse
enters, when we wanna add will-change,
当他们点击时，我们想要添加这个类。
when they click,
we want to add this class.
然后当鼠标离开的时候，过渡结束的地方，也就是我们把
And then when the mouse leaves, where the
transition ends, that will be when we put
它回到了自己的层，因为我们是浏览器社区中的好公民。
it back on its own layer because we are
good citizens in the browser community.